(gentle electronic music)
So we learned before that Node.js
is all about asynchronous code,
which was traditionally implemented
using callback functions, right?
However, in modern JavaScript,
we now have some better tools
to deal with asynchronous code,
and these tools are Promises and Async/Await.
So I will use Promises and Async/Await
in this entire course now,
well, because, that's just the way
modern Node.js code is written,
and so if you're not entirely familiar with these new tools,
well, then please go ahead and watch this short section
which will bring you up to speed
with asynchronous JavaScript.
But of course, if you already know Promises and Async/Await,
then feel free to just entirely skip this section.